

291, Daehak-ro, Yuseong-gu, Daejeon, Rep. of Korea

🛮 (+82) 10-6484-5597 | 💌 m1n9yu@kaist.ac.kr | 🌃 https://gyuhub.github.io | 🖸 gyuhub | 🛅 mngupark | 💆 @mngupark | 🎓 Mingyu Park

"True failure is what not trying to challenge, not what you couldn't overcome today."

Summary

My research goal is to build **real-world** robots that can perform control tasks with human-level abilities and generalize to unseen situations using artificial general intelligence (AGI). I'm especially interested in developing practical methods for sequential decision-making problems. My current mission toward this goal is to devise a general method that can recover an expert policy from static datasets under high-dimensional sensory input. Formally, my research interest interleaves between offline reinforcement learning, self-supervised learning, and foundation models.

Education

Kwangwoon University

Mar. 2017 - Feb. 2023

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS • Total GPA: 4.18/4.50 Major GPA: 4.43/4.50

KAIST (Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology)

Mar. 2023 - Now

M.S. IN ROBOTICS PROGRAM

- Advised by Prof. Dongwhan Lee
- Total GPA: 3.94/4.30

Experience

KIST (Korea Institute of Science and Techonoloy)

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Jun. 2021 - Dec. 2021

- Implemented an optimal control system of the fixed-base redundant dual-arm manipulators.
- Implemented a ROS framework to the manipulator system.
- Researched a method that can reduce the computational cost of the optimal controller for real-time control.

Seoul National University (DYROS, Dynamics Robotics Systems Lab)

UNDERGRADUATE RESEARCH INTERN

Jan. 2022 - Oct. 2022

- Researched a mobile robot navigation system using SLAM and extended Kalman filter.
- Researched an efficient map construction using multiple sensors on a single robot.
- Researched a whole-body controller using hierarchical quadratic programming for a mobile manipulator system.

KAIST (MDILRG, Machine Decision Intelligence and Learning Research Group)

Mar. 2023 - Now

GRADUATE STUDENT

- Researched a combination of the dueling architecture and alternative max operators.

· Researched a method that can leverage a pretrained model to enable better initialization for offline RL.

Publications

JOURNAL

• Park, M., Kim, D., Oh, Y., Lee, Y. (2022). Computational Cost Reduction Method for HQP-based Hierarchical Controller for Articulated Robot. The Journal of Korea Robotics Society, 17(1), 16-24.

Skills_

Programming Languages Python, C, C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Frameworks Robot Operating System (ROS) 1 & 2, Matlab, Docker, Tensorflow, PyTorch, Jax

Simulators Gazebo, MuJoCo, CoppeliaSim, Raisim, IsaacSim

Languages Korean, English, Japanese

Extracurricular Activity ___

MINGYU PARK · CURRICULUM VITAE APRIL 25, 2024

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group in Kwangwoon University)

S.Korea

 CORE MEMBER
 Mar. 2020 - Dec. 2022

- Gained academic knowledge related to robotics such as computer vision and control engineering.
- Gained expertise in crafting a robot from scratch and insight to analyze complex systems.
- Obtained leadership and supervised group members serving as club director.

Scholarships & Awards

SCHOLARSHIPS

Feb. 2017 Kwangwoon Dream , Admission Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Oct. 2017 Kwangwoon Dream, Admission Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Oct. 2020 Quarter tuition scholarship, Academic Excellence Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Feb. 2021 Full tuition scholarship, Academic Excellence Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Oct. 2021 Half tuition scholarship, Academic Excellence Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Oct. 2022 Half tuition scholarship, Academic Excellence Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
\\ \ADDC	

AWARDS

Feb. 2021 Dean's List, Academic Excellence Award	Seoul, S.Kored
Oct. 2021 Dean's List , Academic Excellence Award	Seoul, S.Kored
Oct. 2022 Dean's List , Academic Excellence Award	Seoul, S.Kored